(Q1) Thorndyke's.
Good morning. Is that Mr Thorndyke?
Speaking. How can I help?
I've got quite a few things which need painting and fixing in the flat and I wonder whether you'd be able to do the work.
I'm sure I'd be able to help but let me take down a few details.
Yes, of course.
Well, firstly, how did you hear about us?
(Qexample) It was my friend May Hampton ... you did some excellent work for her a couple of years ago. Do you remember?
Oh, yes, that was in West Park Flats, lovely lady.
Yes, she is.
And what's your name, please?
It's Edith Pargetter.
Edith ... can you spell your surname, please? Edith……
[Q1答案句] It's P-A-R-G-E-double T-E-R.
Double T, right.
(Q2) And do you live in West Park Flats as well?
[Q2答案句] No, actually it's East Park, Flat 4.
(Q3) Oh, right, that's over the road, I seem to remember - quite difficult to get to.
[Q3答案句] Yes. it's at the back of the library.
(Q4) Right, I know. And what's your phone number?
875934 but I'm out a great deal in the afternoons and evenings.
[Q4答案句] So would the best time to ring you be in the morning?
[Q4答案句-确认] Yes.
(Q5) Fine. I've made a note of that. Can I just ask, I'll be in a van and I know parking's rather difficult round your flats.
Where would you recommend?
[Q5答案句] Well. I always tell people in larger vehicles to park by the postbox on the other side of the road from the entrance.
Good, thanks.
(Q6) And will you be able to give me a full itemised quote?
[Q6答案句] Oh. Yes, I'll list all the jobs separately with individual prices.
That'd be a great help.
No problem.
(Q7（table横纵表格填空）) Now, what would you like me to do?
Firstly and most urgently is in the kitchen.
With all the weather damage, the glass in the door has cracked and I'd need that fixing ...
I presume you mean replacing?
Oh, yes. And as soon as possible ...
What I'll do is come round tomorrow morning and do that immediately.
Thank you so much. The other things aren't so urgent but...
Now, I'll make a note of everything you want doing.
Well, in the kitchen I'd like some painting doing.
All the kitchen walls?
Just the area over the cooker. It's very greasy ...
Right ...it does tend to get that way!
Yes!
Well, if you want a proper job done what I'd need to do is strip the old paint and plaster it about a week before I paint it.
Of course. Now, May tells me you also do work in the garden.
That's right.
Well. I'd like you to replace a fence.
Just one?
Yes, at the far end.
Fine. Shouldn't be a problem.
And that's the lot.
Fine. Yeah, as I say I can come round tomorrow morning to look over things with you.
That's great, thank you.
So, I'll look forward to seeing you tomorrow at...